(Leonard:)In my head.
(chuckles)
(Leonard:)On the way home.
(Leonard:)While I was having a good cry.
(knocking on door)
(Amy:)Sheldon, can I come in?
(Sheldon:)I don't think
that's a good idea.
(Amy:)Why not?
(Sheldon:)According to an online
message board,
(Sheldon:)I may be having a panic attack.
(Sheldon:)SoccerMom09 had
similar symptoms.
(Sheldon:)But to be fair, the twins were
a real handful that day.
(Amy:)You're making me worry.
(Amy:)What's going on?
(Sheldon:)What's going on is we're
about to go to a prom.
(Sheldon:)And there's
a great deal of pressure
(Sheldon:)on young couples
like us to engage in
(Sheldon:)what Mr. Bob Eubanks
called making whoopee.
(Amy:)What pressure?
(Amy:)All I said was
you look handsome.
(Amy:)Can you please
open the door?
(Sheldon:)It's not just that.
(Sheldon:)Leonard and Penny also
made comments about it.
(Sheldon:)And I'm not blind.
(Sheldon:)Even I looked twice
when I saw my posterior